Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Annotated, not numbered
      - E-H
        - Hipsway - The honeythief, 1986; SR-26567; Hipsway (Box 38)
          Catalog # 44 05988; A-side Matrix # XSS-173993-1A
        - Hitmen - 4 songs from "Torn Together", 1981; SR-26568; Hitmen (Box 38)
          Catalog # AS 1300; A-side Matrix # XSM168808-1A
        - Hodge, James And Smith - Incredible, 1973; SR-26569; Hodge, James And Smith; Stevenson, Wm. (Box 38)
          Catalog # T-425; A-side Matrix # M-425-AS
        - Hoggard, Jay - Rain forest, 1981; SR-26570; Hoggard, Jay (Box 38)
          Catalog # 14007; A-side Matrix # LKS 365-D1A
          Contemporary Records
        - Holliday, Jennifer - Feel my soul, 1983; SR-26571; Holliday, Jennifer (Box 38)
          Catalog # GHS 4014; A-side Matrix # GHS-1-4014-SH3 B-18451-SH3 SLM SP 5082
          Geffen Records
        - Holloway, Loleatta - Queen of the night, 1978; SR-26572; Holloway, Loleatta (Box 38)
          Catalog # GA 9501 DJ; A-side Matrix # GA 9501 A
        - Holman, Eddie - A night to remember, 1994; SR-26573; Holman, Eddie (Box 38)
          Catalog # CPLP 8061; A-side Matrix # CPLP 8061 A
          Charly Records
        - Holme - Just a matter of time, 1982; SR-26574; Holme; Mazur, Mark (Box 38)
          Catalog # DRZ 7101; A-side Matrix # DRZ-7101-A
          Drive Records
        - Holmes, Rupert - Pursuit of happiness, 1978; SR-26575; Holmes, Rupert (Box 38)
          Catalog # PS 7006; A-side Matrix # PS-7006A
          Private Stock
        - Holt '45 - Ain't got time; Hot love, 1980; SR-26576; Holt '45 (Box 38)
          In same jacket as # SR-26577. 2 copies.
          Catalog # SUD 002; A-side Matrix # VRC-30001-A
          Sutra Records
        - Holt '45 - Ain't got time; Hot love, 1980; SR-26577; Holt '45 (Box 38)
          In same jacket as # SR-26576. 2 copies.
          Catalog # VRC 30001; A-side Matrix # VRC-30001-1
          Virile Records
        - HomeBoyz - It's your night, 1985; SR-26578; HomeBoyz; Renny (Box 38)
          In same jacket as # SR-26579. 2 copies.
          Catalog # JS 9990; A-side Matrix # 511073X-A
          Jes Say Records
        - HomeBoyz - It's your night, 1985; SR-26579; HomeBoyz; Renny (Box 38)
          In same jacket as # SR-26578. 2 copies.
        - Honey B's - Honey B's, 1982; SR-26580; Honey B's (Box 38)
          Catalog # DUPLA 5003; A-side Matrix # DUPLA5003-A
          Transistor
        - Honey Cone - Soulful tapestry, 1971; SR-26581; Honey Cone (Box 38)
          Catalog # HA 707; A-side Matrix # HA707A-11
          Hot Wax
        - Hooper, Eddie - Pass it on, 1979; SR-26582; Hooper, Eddie; Storm (Box 38)
          Catalog # HCH-001; A-side Matrix # HCH-001-A
          HCH Records
        - Horan, Eddie - Love the way you love me, 1978; SR-26583; Horan, Eddie (Box 38)
          Catalog # HDM-2002; A-side Matrix # HDM-2002-1
          HDM Records
        - Horne, Jimmy "Bo" - "Bo" Horne '91, 1991; SR-26584; Horne, Jimmy "Bo" (Box 38)
          Catalog # NMLP 1024; A-side Matrix # NMLP 1024 A
          New Music International
          Milan, Italy
        - Horne, Jimmy "Bo" - Goin' home for love, 1979; SR-26585; Horne, Jimmy "Bo" (Box 38)
          In same jacket as # SR-26586. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 7805; A-side Matrix # SSE-7805-A (7)
          Sunshine Sound
        - Horne, Jimmy "Bo" - Goin' home for love, 1979; SR-26586; Horne, Jimmy "Bo" (Box 38)
          In same jacket as # SR-26585. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 7805; A-side Matrix # SSE-7805-AX-(1)
        - Horsemen - Pimphouse all-stars II, 1997; SR-26587; Horsemen; Big Ria (Box 38)
          In same jacket as # SR-26588. 2 copies.
          Catalog # PM6011; A-side Matrix # PM-6011-SIDE UNO
          Pimphouse Music
          Baltimore, Maryland
        - Horsemen - Pimphouse all-stars II, 1997; SR-26588; Horsemen; Big Ria (Box 38)
          In same jacket as # SR-26587. 2 copies.
        - Horsemen - Pimphouse all stars # III, 1997; SR-26589; Horsemen; Big Ria (Box 38)
          Catalog # PM6014; A-side Matrix # PM-6014-SIDE A RADIO
        - Hot Chocolate - Every 1's a winner, 1978; SR-26590; Hot Chocolate (Box 38)
          Catalog # INF-9002; A-side Matrix # INF-9002-A
          Infinity Records
        - Hot Chocolate - Going through the motions, 1979; SR-26591; Hot Chocolate (Box 38)
          Catalog # INF 16,004; A-side Matrix # INF-16004-A
        - Hot Cuisine - Who's been kissing you?; All fired up, 1981; SR-26592; Hot Cuisine (Box 38)
          In same jacket as # SR-26593. 2 copies.
          Catalog # PRL D 531; A-side Matrix # PRLD-531-A
        - Hot Cuisine - Who's been kissing you?, 1981; SR-26593; Hot Cuisine (Box 38)
          In same jacket as # SR-26592. 2 copies.
          Catalog # PRL D 613; A-side Matrix # PRLD-613-A
        - Hot Day - It's my turn, 1989; SR-26594; Hot Day; Franklin, Dante (Box 38)
          Catalog # TUF LP 0559; A-side Matrix # TUFLP-0559-A
        - Houston, Thelma - Working girl, 1983; SR-26595; Houston, Thelma (Box 38)
          Catalog # MCA-13963; A-side Matrix # MCA-3341-FDS-1
        - Houston, Thelma - If you feel it, 1981; SR-26596; Houston, Thelma (Box 38)
          Catalog # JD-12216; A-side Matrix # PD-12216A 2S
        - Howard, Adina - It's all about you, 1995; SR-26597; Howard, Adina (Box 38)
          In same jacket as # SR-26598
          Catalog # ED 5811; A-side Matrix # 2TED 5811-A
          EastWest Records America
        - Howard, Adina - It's all about you, 1995; SR-26598; Howard, Adina (Box 38)
          In same jacket as # SR-26597
        - Howard, Miki - Come share my love, 1986; SR-26599; Howard, Miki (Box 38)
          Catalog # 81688-1; A-side Matrix # ST A 866145 A
        - Hudmon, R.B. - Closer to you, 1978; SR-26600; Hudmon, R.B. (Box 38)
          Catalog # SD 5204; A-side Matrix # ST-CTN 774005-A
        - Hudson, Ronnie - West cost poplock, 1982; SR-26601; Hudson, Ronnie; Ronnie Hudson And The Street People (Box 39)
          In same jacket as # SR-26602. Different discs.
          Catalog # BD 1002; A-side Matrix # SP-1000-A
          Birdie
        - Hudson, Ronnie - East coast poplock, 1982; SR-26602; Hudson, Ronnie; Ronnie Hudson And The Street People (Box 39)
          In same jacket as # SR-26601. Different discs.
          Catalog # STP 1003 A; A-side Matrix # STP1003A
          Street People Record Co.
        - Hula - Poison, 1986; SR-26603; Hula (Box 39)
          Catalog # RED T74; A-side Matrix # REDT 74 A1
          Red Rhino Records
          York, United Kingdom
        - Hula - Walk on stalks of shattered glass, 1985; SR-26604; Hula (Box 39)
          Catalog # RED T.62; A-side Matrix # RED T 62 A1
        - Human Nature - You are the one, 1984; SR-26605; Human Nature (Box 39)
          Catalog # SKDS-1118; A-side Matrix # 1118-A
          Streetking Records
        - Humble Pie - Smokin', 1972; SR-26606; Humble Pie (Box 39)
          Catalog # SP-4342; A-side Matrix # A&M SP4583(RE-1)-P4
        - Hummingbird - Diamond nights, 1977; SR-26607; Hummingbird (Box 39)
          Catalog # SP-4661; A-side Matrix # A&M SP5059(RE-1)-T2
          Beverly Hills, California
        - Hunt, Geraldine - Can't fake the feeling, 1980; SR-26608; Hunt, Geraldine (Box 39)
          In same jacket as # SR-26609. 2 copies.
          Catalog # PDS-405; A-side Matrix # PDS-405-A
        - Hunt, Geraldine - Can't fake the feeling, 1980; SR-26609; Hunt, Geraldine (Box 39)
          In same jacket as # SR-26608. 2 copies.
        - Hunter, Ian - All American alien boy, 1976; SR-26610; Hunter, Ian (Box 39)
          Catalog # C 34142; A-side Matrix # PAL 34142-2E
        - Huntsberry, Howard - Sleepless weekend, 1988; SR-26611; Huntsberry, Howard (Box 39)
          Catalog # L33-17714; A-side Matrix # MCA8429 FDS-4
        - Hurt 'em Bad And The S.C. Band - Monday night football, 1982; SR-26612; Hurt 'em Bad And The S.C. Band (Box 39)
          Catalog # PRO-7011; A-side Matrix # PB PRO-7011A-1
          Profile Records
        - Hustler - Play loud, 1975; SR-26613; Hustler (Box 39)
          Catalog # SP-4556; A-side Matrix # AM SP 4849 P1
        - Hustlers of Culture - Kickin' off, 1996; SR-26614; Hustlers of Culture (Box 39)
          Catalog # WALLT 015; A-side Matrix # WALL T 015-A1
          Wall Of Sound
        - Hutch, Willie - Midnight dancer, 1979; SR-26615; Hutch, Willie (Box 39)
          Catalog # WHK 3352; A-side Matrix # WHK-1-3352 LW3
          Whitfield Records
        - Hutson, Leroy - The man!, 1995; SR-26616; Hutson, Leroy (Box 39)
          Catalog # CPLP 8128; A-side Matrix # CPLP 8128 A1
          Charly Groove
        - Hutson, Leroy - Love oh love, 1995; SR-26617; Hutson, Leroy (Box 39)
          Catalog # CPLP 8156; A-side Matrix # CPLP 8156 A1
        - Hyman, Phyllis - Living all alone, 1986; SR-26618; Hyman, Phyllis (Box 39)
          Catalog # ST-53029; A-side Matrix # ST-1-53029 Z2
          Philadelphia International Rceords
        - Hyman, Phyllis - You know how to love me, 1979; SR-26619; Hyman, Phyllis (Box 39)
          Catalog # SP-75; A-side Matrix # SP-75-SA
        - Hyman, Phyllis - Tonight you and me, 1981; SR-26620; Hyman, Phyllis (Box 39)
          Catalog # SP 114; A-side Matrix # SP-114-SAS-T1
        - Hydro - I'll make your day tonight; K.I.C. (Keep it coming), 1979; SR-26621; Hydro; Lorna (Box 39)
          In same jacket as # SR-26622. 2 copies.
          Catalog # PDS 401; A-side Matrix # PDS-401-B
        - Hydro - I'll make your day tonight; K.I.C. (Keep it coming), 1979; SR-26622; Hydro; Lorna (Box 39)
          In same jacket as # SR-26621. 2 copies.
        - Hydro - Hydro featuring Lorna, 1979; SR-26623; Hydro; Lorna (Box 39)
          Catalog # PLP 1003; A-side Matrix # PLP 1003 A
        - Hydrophonix - Burning up; Here and now in '98, 1998; SR-26624; Hydrophonix (Box 39)
          Catalog # HYD-001; A-side Matrix # HYD-001-A-1
          PK Records
          Orlando, Florida
        - Hysterica Passio - Grey over life, 1982; SR-26625; Hysterica Passio (Box 39)
          Catalog # 16457; A-side Matrix # 16457-A
          Fire in Heart Music